Week 6. Day 1. Fair fashion. Process. Artisan. Craft. Quality. Trainer. Jewelry. Worldwide.
Scholarship. Otherwise. Proudly. Purchase. Day 2. Frida Kahlo's paintings and psychology.
Psychology. Extraordinary. Suffering. Energetic. Vibrant. Majority. Self-portrait. Represent.
Being. Politically. Bold. Imagery. Combine. Hold back. Day 3. The Naza Lines of Peru.
Flat. Sketch. Hummingbird. Alien. Civilization. Evidence. Experiment. Organize. Relatively.
Point 2. Agreement. Ancient Monument. Appreciate. Marvelant. Accomplishment. Ancestor. Day 4. Are
you addicted to the Internet? Addicted. Controversial. Disorder. Compulsive. Hook. Gambling. Chore.
Relief. Dependent. Intend. Day 5. Hold on to your pocket money. Hold onto. Budget. Allowance. Total. Period.
Transportation. Priority. Add up. Tempt. Expense. Change. Day 6. Asperger's Syndrome. Syndrome.
Astonish. Recall. Expression. Autism. Let alone. Cure. Ramble on. Eye contact. Emotional. Affectionate.